Oh.
Fast and loud the strings ignite Running wild on Frisco night History folks with missing legs McCoyotes creeping back through time Never thought they'd roam again Past the bridges, city bends We drove them out in olden days But hung their finds each modern way Stealing fog, the golden gate Open pathway, shipping fate They're marrying the maid, they're playing Spreads the past, it's not the same Lives are drawn in yards and hearts Sidewalk beatings, dog bark barks Debate in every wobble bar Are we safe for Hoibor?
Out on the streets again, Coyote's running free San Francisco's shaping up the old history Some mare in made shape, flaccid red steel frame Never city twist, two sides of step, Coyote game Cow with the night Cow with the night
Back in the day went the wave one thousand eight hundred and ninety-five We thought Big Dippy gone but San Francisco survives Fleeking from the forest riding on the northbound wind Sneaked through the Presidio, a rig was oncoming Some push their dogs tight, keep the backyard light Kids Austin blasts, beer and yawns there at night Others see ballots, Matron patrol Clearing out the rats, chasing cats, filling up the hall
Out on the streets again, Coyotes running free.
San Francisco's shaking out beyond history.
From Mayor in Main Street, Schwoz and Rats feel free.
Then the city flits two signs out, it's the Coyote Game.
Out with the night.